A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Abe Fellowships, Record Group 3, Series 8 FA1871
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council records, Abe Fellowships, Record Group 3, Series 8
1983-1995
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council
FA1871
10.26 Cubic Feet 27 document boxes: 27 letter size boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to the RAC from the Social Science Research Council as part of several different accessions between 2016 and 2017. These accessions were ingested as Accession 2016:003, 2016:005, 2016:009, 2016:010, 2016:074, 2016:075, 2017:017, 2017:018, 2017:024.
Arrangement
Series 8 of Record Group 3 consists of 6 subseries.
Series arrangement is as follows:
Subseries 8.1 Fellowship applicant awardees files, 1991-1993
Subseries 8.2 Fellowship applicant declinations and withdrawals files, 1983-1994
Subseries 8.3 Fellowship applicant review general files, 1989-1992
Subseries 8.4 Chronology files, 1991-1995
Subseries 8.5 Meeting files, 1989-1995
Subseries 8.6 Budget files, 1991-1995
Files documenting individual Abe Fellowship applicants were arranged into their own subseries with distinctions between files where applicants were awarded a fellowship and files where applicants were not reflected in subseries assignments. The fellowship files in Subseries 8.1 and 8.2 are ordered by the year of the fellowship award.
Biographical / Historical
The Abe Fellowship Program was a collaboration between the Social Science Research Council (SSRC) and the Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP). Administered by the SSRC and the American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), the Program awarded fellowships for multidisciplinary research on global issues and problem solving and strived to promote intellectual cooperation between Japan and the United States. The Program ran from 1991 to 2022.
Citizens from Japan and the United States could apply for the fellowship as well as scholars from other countries who demonstrated relationships to research communities in either nation. Applicants were required to have a Ph.D. or terminal degree.
During the early years of the program, fellowships concerned three research themes. These themes were: 1) Global issues; 2) Problems common amongst developed, industrialized countries; and 3) Issues relating to improving United States-Japan relations.
Later research themes included: 1) Threats to Personal, Societal, and International Security; 2) Growth and Sustainable Development; 3) Social, Scientific, and Cultural Trends and Transformations; and 4) Governance, Empowerment, and Participation.
Scope and Contents
This series contains the files of the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) Abe Fellowship Program. The Abe Fellowship Program was a collaboration between the SSRC and the Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP). It was administered by the SSRC and the American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS). Fellowships were awarded to Japanese and United States citizens as well as scholars from other countries who demonstrated relationships to research communities in either nation. The fellowships were for multidisciplinary research on global issues and problem solving and were meant to promote intellectual cooperation between Japan and the United States.
This series is comprised of 6 subseries. Most of the series' contents document the Abe Fellowship Program Committee's review of fellowship applications. The first three subseries contain files devoted to the applicant review of several fellowship competitions. Subseries 1 contains files for applicants who were awarded a fellowship, and Subseries 2 contains files for applicants who were declined a fellowship or withdrew from competition. More general files pertaining to application review are contained in Subseries 3.
Smaller sets of records are contained in the other three subseries. Subseries 4 contains a run of chronology files for incoming and outgoing SSRC correspondence regarding the Abe Fellowship Program. Meeting files in Subseries 5 regard different meetings and conferences organized by the Program. Lastly, Subseries 6 contains files concerning the Program's budget and expense tracking.
Fellowship applications and other materials show the broad range of topics applicants and awarded fellows pursued in relation to the Program's research themes during these years of its operations. These themes were: 1) Global issues; 2) Problems common amongst developed, industrialized countries; 3) and Issues relating to improving United States-Japan relations.
Research subjects included:
- International security, peace keeping, conflict resolution; Japan's role in the United Nations in relation to these concerns; changes to international security in the post-Cold War Era; and various international conflicts
- International relations, specifically in relation to the Japan-United States relationship, Northeast Asia, and the Asia Pacific region; international aid; and international organizations
- International trade and economic relations; industries, management, and labor; and financial regulation
- Aging, elderly people, and retired workers; and demographic changes
- Perceptions and depictions of Japan and Japanese people outside of Japan
- The environment, natural resources, and climate change
- Culture, arts, media, and literature
- Immigration; people of Japanese heritage in countries outside of Japan; and other ethnic groups in Japan
- Other topics like education, women, religion, technology, politics, agriculture, and family studies
Numerous SSRC staff members were involved in the creation of these records including Helen Chauncey, Vanessa Vinarub, Jennifer Bourque, Mary Brynne McDonnell, Sheri Ranis, Minami Toshiyuki, Shiela Smith, Dee Warren, and Mary-Lea Cox.
Common material formats found throughout the collection, in addition to the aforementioned formats, include memos, drafts, notes, reports, meeting briefing books and agendas, invoices, and articles.
Japan; East Asia; United States; Older people; Peace-building; Security, International; Sociology
- Fellowship applicant awardee files, 1991-1993; 1; .665 Cubic Feet 1.75 document boxes: 1.75 letter boxes
  Scope and Contents
  This subseries contains Abe Fellowship Program Committee applicant files for applications awarded fellowships by the Committee. The files document the earliest competitions of the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) Abe Fellowship Program. They span from 1991 to 1994.
  There are no award letters included in the files. Research was done during the processing of the collection to verify what applicants were awarded through consulting the SSRC's Items newsletter archive. Some of these files include a small amount of correspondence that discusses the awardee's fellowship.
  The files are chiefly comprised of the application materials which include the application forms, application checklists, project statements, letters of reference, and budget forms. Some files include additional correspondence.
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Caldwell, John (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Cornelius, Wayne (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Gilpin, Robert G. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Hamada, Tomoko (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Hanson, Richard (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Ivanov, Vladimir I. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Kawato, Sadafumi (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Kubo, Fumiaki (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees – Lee, Hiro (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees – Lewis, Catherine (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees – Lillehoj, Elizabeth (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees – Muryama, Yuki (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Rosefielde, Steven S. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Weinstein, David (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 awardees - Yamagishi, Toshio (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Adachi, Kiyoshi (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Asakura, Yuko (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Awanohara, Susumu (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Bestor, Theodore (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Callon, Scott (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Campbell, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Evans, Robert (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - George, Aurelia (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Graven, Kathryn J. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Hiwatari, Nobuhiro (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Kurokawa, Susumu (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Marsh, James (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Schaede, Ulrike (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Schear, James A. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Sherman, Spencer (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Sundaram, Jomo Kwame (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Takeda, Yu (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Tsuda, Mamoru (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Watanabe, Shin (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 awardees - Wetherfield, Alison, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Fellowship applicant declinations and withdrawals files, 1983-1994; 2; 6.175 Cubic Feet 16.25 document boxes: 16.25 letter boxes
  This subseries contains Abe Fellowship Program Committee applicant files for applications declined fellowships by the Committee or were withdrawn by the applicants. The files document the earliest competitions of the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) Abe Fellowship Program. They span from 1991 to 1995.
  The files are chiefly comprised of letters from the Program declining the application and the application materials. The application materials include the application forms, application checklists, project statements, letters of reference, and budget forms. Some files include additional correspondence.
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Abe, Kiyoshi (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Abe, Yukiko (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Al-Marayati, Abid A. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Amstutz, Galen (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Anderson, Fred E. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Anegawa, Tomofumi (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Anderson, Stephen J. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Ariki, Soichiro (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Arima, Midori (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Benes, Nicholas E. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Berberoglu, Berch (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Bohrer, Stephen (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Bornstein, Lisa (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Brennan, Maura Jo (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Brenner, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Burns, Patrick D (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Cameron, Carrie A. (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Chiba, Shin (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Cleveland, Kyle (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Coleman, Samuel (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Cross, Larry R. (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - The Curators of the University of Missouri (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Dethloff, Henry C. (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Elashmawi, Farid, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Endicott, John E. (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Fand, David (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Feldman, Stuart, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Florig, Dennis (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Freitas, Deborah Inman (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Fukai, Shigeko (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Fukuda, Shin-ichi (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Gelb, Joyce (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Gier, Nicholas F. (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Gilday, Edmund T. (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Golin, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Goto, Junko (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Guterbock, T.M., 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Hanawa, Yukiko (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations- Harootunian, Harry (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Hart, Gillian (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Heshiki, Kazumi (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Higashimoto, Haruo (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Higuchi, Norio (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Hines, Mary Alice (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Hojo, Hiroo (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Ifeajuna, Lawson Osita (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Iida, Keisuke (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Inada, Juichi (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Inokuchi, Hiromitsu (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Ishida, Hiroshi (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Ishida, Tsuyoshi (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kajimoto, Takeo (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kamioka, Nobuo (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kato, Junko (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kawano, Hitoshi (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kawasaki, Tsuyoshi (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Khan, Yoshimitsu (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kimura, Masahiro (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kingston, Jeffrey B. (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kishimia, Takako (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Koga, Tetsuo (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kohno, Masaru (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Koizumi, Shigeko (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Korukonda, Appa R. (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kotby, Hussein E. (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Kume, Ikuo (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Lie, John (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Lye, Diane (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Lynch, Tim (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Mabuchi, Noritoshi (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Machida, Sandra (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – MacDougall, Terry (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Markin, Terrance (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Masterson, Daniel (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Matsuda, Takeshi (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Matsuoka, Hideaki (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Meuth, Elizabeth (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – McConnell, David (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Minami, Hirofumi (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Mezur, Katherine (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Mikanagi, Yumiko (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Miller, Alan S. (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Mitake, Naoya (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Morton, Leith (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Mourdoukoutas, Panos (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Murphy-Shigematsu, Stephen (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Nafziger, E. Wayne (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Nakashima, Yasuhiro (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Newcomb, Horace (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Ane Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Nishitani, Hajime (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Nishiyama, Toshiaki (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Nitta, Michio (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Noer, John (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Ohno, Kenichi (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Ohki, Sadako (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Okamoto, Koichi (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Olson, Jerry (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Orr, Bill (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Osawa, Machiko (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Oshiba, Ryo (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Painter, Andrew A. (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Pasricha, Sadhana (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Philson, Richard, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Pinpin-Feinstein, Maria Victoria (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Rao, J. Mohan (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Reich, Pauline C., 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Renshaw, Jean (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Rosen, Daniel A. (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Rozman, Gilbert (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Sakuragawa, Masaya (Box 9, Folder 145)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Sasaki, Yoshitaka (Box 9, Folder 146)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Shionoya, Yuichi (Box 9, Folder 147)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Shirai, Sayuri (Box 9, Folder 148)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Skaer, Peter M. (Box 9, Folder 149)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Smith, Herman W. (Box 9, Folder 150)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Sone, Akio (Box 9, Folder 151)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Stadler, Ingrid (Box 9, Folder 152)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Steen, Tomoko Y. (Box 9, Folder 153)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Steslicke, William E. (Box 10, Folder 154)